Guide to the Collection of Type Specimens
Yale University Arts Library
- Typeface, Series I
  - Times Series, American Wood Type Mfg. Co. (distributor), Stanley Morison, undated; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Torino, Advertising Agencies' Service Co., undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Torino, Amsterdam Continental (distributor), Nebiolo Type Foundry, undated; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Torino, Composing Room, undated; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Torino, Lettering Inc., undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Tourist Gothic, Lanston Monotype, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trade Gothic, Mergenthaler Linotype, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trafton Script, Bauer Type Foundry, Howard Trafton, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trajan, Adobe, 1989; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trajanus, Stempel Typefounders, Warren Chappell, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trooper Roman, Visual Graphics Corporation, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Trump Imperial, Huxley House Ltd., Georg Trump, undated; 3 (Box 4)
  - Trump Mediaeval, Amsterdam Continental, Georg Trump, 1968; 1 (Box 4)
  - Trump Mediaeval, The Stinehour Press (distributor), Mergenthaler Linoterm, 1980; 1 (Box 4)
  - Trump Mediaeval, C.E. Weber Typefoundry, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Ultra Bodoni, American Type Founders, 1928-1930; 1 (Box 9)
  - Univers, American Type Founders (distributor), Deberny et Peignot, Adrian Frutiger, 1968; 4 (Box 4)
  - Univers, The Monotype Corporation (distributor), Adrian Frutiger, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - University Series, Mergenthaler, 1976, 1 (Box 4)
  - Usherwood, International Typeface Corporation, 1984; 2 (Box 4)
  - Utopia, Adobe, 1989; 2 (Box 4)
  - Van Dijck, The Monotype Corporation, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Veljovic, International Typeface Corporation, 1984; 3 (Box 4)
  - Venus, Bauer Alphabets, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Venus Extended, Philmac Typographers, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Verona, American Type Founders, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Verona, Stephenson Blake, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Viva, Adobe, 1993; 1 (Box 4)
  - Vogue, Intertype, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Walbaum, Amsterdam Continental (distributor), Berthold Type Foundry, undated; 1 (Box 4)
  - Waverly, Intertype, 1941; 1 (Box 4)
  - Weidemann, International Typeface Corporation, 1983; 3 (Box 4)
  - Weiss, Bauer Alphabets, 1977; 1 (Box 4)
  - Weiss Antiqua, Bauersche Giesserei, E.R. Weiss, 1929; 1 (Box 4)
  - Wood Type I, Adobe, 1990; 2 (Box 4)
  - Wood Type II, Adobe, 1990; 2 (Box 4)
  - Wood Type III, Adobe, 1994, 1 (Box 4)
  - Zapf Book, International Typeface Corporation, Hermann Zapf, 1976; 6 (Box 4)
  - Zapf Chancery Series, International Typeface Corporation, Hermann Zapf, 1979; 1 (Box 9)
  - Zapf Dingbats, International Typeface Corporation, 1978; 4 (Box 4)
  - Zapf International, International Typeface Corporation, Hermann Zapf, 1977; 5 (Box 4)
  - Zeppelin, Continental Typefounders Assn., undated; 1 (Box 4)
- Manufacturer, Series II
  This series is ordered alphabetically by the name of manufacturer. Individual items contained in each file are listed below the manufacturer's name.
  Please note that the series begins with an "Anonymous" file and ends with an "Unidentified" file.
  - Anonymous, undated (Box 9)
  - Aaron Burns & Co., Inc. (Box 4)
    - Type Faces / edition number one, undated
    - Typositor Typography / a new typograph, undated
    - Fifteen Award Winning Type Face Design, undated
  - Adobe Systems Incorporated (Box 4)
    - Adobe Type 1 Multiple Master Typefaces, 1991
  - Advertising Agencies' Service Company, Inc. (Box 4)
    - More Than 300 Type Faces Available for Distinctive Advertising Typography, undated
  - Advertising Alphabets Inc. (Box 4)
    - Low Cost Paste-Up Catalog of Beautiful Type Faces, undated
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts (Box 4)
    - Type Faces and Paper Surfaces, undated
  - American Type Founders, 1913-1962 undated (Box 4)
    - Two-Series Typography, Raleigh Cursive and Modernique, shown in combination, undated
    - The Book of French Types Borders and Ornaments, 1913
    - New Type Faces and Decorative Material for Commercial Printers and Advertising Typographers, 1930; 2
    - Vocational Cameos Showing Many Additional Characters for Modern Printing, 1928
    - Calendar Silhouettes for Calendars, Blotters, and Printing of Many Kinds, 1928
    - Type Advertising Brackets For Modern Typography, undated
    - Typographic Dots, undated
    - A Showing of Brass Rule for Use in Catalogue and Booklet Pages, undated; 3
    - Duratin Metal Rule and ATF Brass Rule, 1943
    - Ornaments Typecast by ATF, 1944
    - ATF Foundry Type Descriptive Price List, 1950; 2 copies
    - ATF Foundry Type Descriptive Price List, 1951
    - ATF Typographic Accessories Specimen Catalog and Price List, 1962
    - Print American ATF Typographic Accessories Specimen Catalog, undated
    - ATF Handypacks Fonts of Shaded Stars and Ombree Ornaments, undated
    - Type Faces Descriptive Index and Price List of ATF Type Foundry Products, undated
    - ATF Handy Type Index, undated; 2
    - New Type Faces, undated; 3
    - Handy Index of American Types, undated
    - Patriotic Typecuts by ATF, undated
    - ATF Typesetter, undated
    - Handy One-Line ATF Type Style Selector with examples of Ornaments and Ideas for their use, undated
    - Type Specimens-Supplement 1, undated
    - Type Specimens-Supplement 2, undated
    - American Type Founders Script and Semiscript Faces, undated
    - American Type Founders Plain Display Gothics, undated
    - Section K Type Specimens, undated
    - Price List of Amsterdam Continental Types, 1950
    - American Type Founders Supplementary Price List, 1951
    - ATF Printing Equipment Catalog, 1959
  - American Wood Type Manufacturing Company (Box 4)
    - American Wood Type Mfg. Co. 1961-62 Catalog, 1961-1962
    - Hand list of Modern display and text types, Stephenson Blake (yellow), undated
    - Hand list of Modern display and text types, Stephenson Blake (orange), undated
    - A Typographical Frolic From S.B.U.K., undated; 2 copies
    - Sans-Gothics, Grotesques and Condensed Series, Stephenson Blake, undated
    - American Wood Type Mfg. Co. broadside, undated
  - Amsterdam Continental (Box 4)
    - New Faces-Fresh Optical Accents!, undated; 3 copies
    - Selection of Amsterdam Continental Type Faces, undated; 2 copies
    - Types from Amsterdam Continental & Graphic Equipment, Inc., representing Europe's leading typefoundries, undated
    - Normande, Tradition, Regina: Berthold Type Faces, undated
    - Nebiolo Typefaces, undated
    - Free lettering styles made by Typefoundry Amsterdam, Holland, undated
    - Four Bold Types to Build Dense Word Images, undated
    - A Survey of Types produced by Typefoundry Amsterdam Distributed by Amsterdam Continental, undated
    - A Survey of Types produced by Berthold Type Foundry distributed by Amsterdam Continental, undated
    - Aigrette/Gracia, undated
    - Caprice/Palette, undated
    - City Bold/Regina, undated
    - Hidalgo/Reiner Script, undated
    - Reiner Black/Boulevard, undated
  - Autologic Incorporated (Box 4)
    - The Anatomy of a Typeface—Media, undated
  - Bache Printing Office (Box 4)
    - A Specimen of Printing Types belonging to Benjamin Franklin Basche's Printing Office, Philadelphia, undated
  - Barnhardt Brothers & Spindler (Box 4)
    - Brass Bodonian Dashes – Penline Flourishes, undated
    - Foreign Language Type Faces, undated
  - Baltimore Type and Composition Company (Box 4)
    - This – Our Catalogue Number 9 Contains a Complete Showing and Pricing of Baltimore Products, 1939
    - BaltoType Price List, 1959
  - Bauer Alphabets Inc. (Box 4)
    - Fonderie de Caracteres Bauer – Catalogue 1938
    - For Your Guidance, undated
    - Foundry Types from Bauer Alphabets, undated
    - Type lore from Stephenson Blake, undated
  - Bauer Type Foundry Inc. (Box 4)
    - To the Club, James!, undated
      General note
      Cover design by Fritz Kredel.
    - Bauer Types, 1950
    - Bauer Types, undated
    - Borders, undated
  - Bernhard (Box 4)
    - Instant Spelling, undated
  - Berthold Type Foundry/H. Berthold A.G. (Box 4)
    - Alt-Motive – Reihenornamente, Zierlinien und Vignetten nach Entwurfen von Hermann Zehnfundt, 1930
    - Mainzer Serie, undated
  - Bertsch & Cooper (Box 4)
    - Bertsch & Cooper present a new type design Cooper Fullface by Oswald Cooper, undated
  - Bitstream Inc. (Box 4)
    - Bitstream Typeface Library, 1989
  - Black Stone Press (Box 4)
    - Explanation of the Point System of Printing Type with Specimens in the Office of the Island City Press, undated
  - Boro Typographers (Box 4)
    - Clarendon postcard, undated
  - Boston Photogravure Co. (Box 4)
    - Catalogue of Illustrations, Designs, Initials, Borders, Etc., 1890
  - Bretzfelder's Printery, undated (Box 4)
  - Brown and Bro. Inc. (Box 4)
    - Quality Self-Sticking Tapes Catalog, undated
  - Brown University Library (Box 4)
    - Examples from the first 25 years of printing in Italy, undated
  - Howard O. Bullard, Inc. (Box 4)
    - Alphabetical arrangement of types and sizes, 1956
  - J.M. Bundscho, Inc (Box 4)
    - Page proofs for inserting in a copy of the Bundscho Type Book, "Here Type Can Serve You", 1951
  - Burns and Company (Box 4)
    - Typography and Lettering, undated
  - Case, Lockwood & Brainard Company (Box 4)
    - Loose Leaf Specimens from Case, Lockwood & Brainard Company, Hartford Connecticut, 1936
  - H.W. Caslon & Company Ltd. (Box 4)
    - Caslon's Old-Fashioned Borders & Bands With a Showing of Modernistic Borders, 1930
    - Specimen's of Caslon Old Face Roman & Italic, undated
    - The Caslon Circular of Complete Service, Summer 1939
  - A.Colish, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Type Specimens Showing Examples of Text Typography for Fine Book Printing, Advertisements & Other Publicity Literature, undated
  - Colton Press, Inc. (Box 4)
    - The Omnibus of Type Faces, 1938
    - "Type Visualizer", 1948
  - Composing Room, Inc. (Box 9)
    - 21 ways to have Texture Type, undated
    - Spartan and Futura, undated
    - De Vinne and Torino, undated
    - Alternate Gothic No. 2 and News Gothic, undated
    - Type Faces, undated
    - Type Faces, 1958
    - Type Faces, 1961
    - Type Faces, 1963; 2
  - Continental Typefounders Association, Inc. (Box 4)
    - A New Half Font Price List, 1931
    - A Selection of Fifty Continental Typefaces, undated; 2 copies
    - A Selection of Types to lend distinction to your work, undated
    - Condensed Specimen Book, undated
    - Continental Type Condensed Specimen Book Second Edition, 1933
    - A Showing of Foundry Types Designed and Cast by Gerb. Klingspor, undated
  - Walter Crittenden (Box 4)
    - Klingspor and Stempel Types, Buffalo, New York, undated
  - Fred A. Crowell, Inc. (Box 4)
    - Specimen Book of Type Faces Ornaments, Borders, Rules, 1938
  - Geo. Damon & Sons (Box 5)
    - Type, Borders, Ornaments, and Brass Rules, undated
  - De Vinne Press (Box 5)
    - Styles of Types for Books and Advertisements Now in Service at The De Vinne Press, 1905
  - Deberny & Peignot (Box 5)
    - Le Sphinx, undated
    - Divertissements Typographiques, 1928
    - Divertissements Typographiques 2, 1929
    - Divertissements Typographiques 3, 1930
  - Paul Hayden Duensing (Box 5)
    - Private Press and Typefoundry of Paul Hayden Duensing, undated
  - Eastern Corporation (Box 5)
    - Alternate Gothic and Franklin Gothic Condensed, specimen sheet designed by Frank Kofron, undated
    - Baskerville, specimen sheet designed by Edwin H. Stuart, Inc.-T.G. Bixler, undated
    - Bernhard Modern, specimen sheet designed by G.H. Petty, undated
    - Calligraphy, specimen sheet designed by Raymond F. DaBoll, undated
    - Caslon, specimen sheet designed by T.M. Cleland, undated
    - Caslon, specimen sheet designed by Carl Purington Rollins, undated
    - Centaur, specimen sheet designed by Bruce Rogers, undated
    - Cheltenham, specimen sheet designed by William Addison Dwiggins, undated
    - Cloister Black, specimen sheet designed by Joseph Thuringer, undated
    - Fairfield, specimen sheet designed by Rudolph Ruzicka, undated
    - Futura, specimen sheet designed by Kurt H. Volk, undated
    - Garamond, specimen sheet designed by Ben Wiley, undated
    - the Lost Goudy Types, specimen sheet designed by Howard Coggeshall, undated
    - concerning Goudy Old Style, specimen sheet designed by Archie J. Little, undated
    - concerning Grayda & Barnum Types, specimen sheet designed by Richard N. McArthur, undated
    - Janson, specimen sheet designed by Fred Anthoensen, undated
    - Lutetia, specimen sheet designed by Edwin and Robert Grabhorn, undated
    - Old-Fashioned Types, specimen sheet designed by Frederic Nelson Phillips, Sr., 1947
    - Perpetua, specimen sheet designed by Helen Gentry, undated
    - Radiant, specimen sheet designed by R. Hunter Middleton, undated
    - Square-Serif Types, specimen sheet designed by Charles R. Jaquish, undated
    - Types Cast by Binny & Ronaldson, specimen sheet designed by P.J. Conkwright, undated
    - Weiss, specimen sheet designed by Ward Ritchie, undated
  - Émigré (Box 5)
    - Type Catalog, undated
  - Joh. Enschede en Zonen (Box 5)
    - Dies Est Laetitiae – A mediaeval Hymn printed from type cast in sand by Joh. Enschede en Zonen, undated
    - Vignetten in Toepassing, 1925
    - Falstaff, undated
    - Lutetia Romein & Cursyf Serie 63 Geteekend door J. Van Krimpen, 1927
    - First Showing of the Lutetia Roman & Italic designed by J. Van Krimpen, undated
  - Robert Estienne (Box 5)
    - Alphabetum Graecum, 1588, undated
  - European Typefounders, Inc. (Box 5)
    - Marathon, undated
    - Price list, undated
    - Sketch, undated
  - Finch Pruyn & Company, Inc. (Box 5)
    - A Finch Focus on Typography, Close-up, no. 1 in a series, undated
    - A Finch Focus on Typography, Bold Close Up, no. 3 in a series, undated
    - A Finch Focus on Typography, the Swingers, no. 5 in a series, undated
    - A Finch Focus on Typography, New Faces, no. 6 in a series, undated
  - Finn Typographic Service, Inc. (Box 5)
    - List of Type Faces, undated
  - Fonderie Peignot & Cie (Box 5)
    - Le Nicholas Cochin Italique, undated
  - Formatt (Box 5)
    - Cut-Out Acetate Graphic Art Aids, undated
  - Franklin Press/Rand, Avery & Co. (Box 5)
    - Fac-simile of "The New England Courant," originally printed by Benjamin Franklin…, 1880
  - J.H. Furst Company (Box 5)
    - A Specimen Book of Type Styles, 1941
  - General Printing Company (Box 5)
    - Type catalog with type available for heads and display, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1930
  - Isaac Goldmann Company (Box 5)
    - Linotype Faces and Borders, undated
  - Graphic Products Corporation (Box 5)
    - Formatt Acetate Graphic Art Aids, catalog no. 4, 1971
    - Formatt Cut-out Acetate Graphic Art Aids, catalog no. 5, 1974
    - Formatt Cut-out Acetate Graphic Art Aids & Formaline Charting & Graphic Art Tapes, catalog no. 6, 1978
  - Gronich Typesetting Service, Inc. (Box 5)
    - Specimen book, undated
  - Groton School Press (Box 5)
    - Specimens of Type, 1925
  - Hamilton Manufacturing Company (Box 9)
    - Catalog No. 22 Complete Information on Modern Time-Saving Equipment for Printing Plants, 1939
    - Catalog No. 27, 1951
    - Some Remarks About Wood Type and Printing Office Furniture, undated
    - Specimens of German Holly Wood Type Manufactured by Hamilton & Baker, undated
    - New Faces in Wood Type Being Most Reproductions of Popular Faces as Cast in Metal, undated
    - Wood Type – New Faces, undated
    - The beautiful series of Cheltenham Faces in 6 widths cut in solid and open, undated
    - Specimens of Hamilton's Wood Type Cut on End-Grain Rock Maple, undated
    - Hamilton's New Series of Roman Borders, undated
  - Headliners International (Box 5)
    - More Morgan A New Collection of Oldstyle Faces, undated
  - Hebrew Press (Box 9)
    - Hebrew Composition with Vowel Points Book, undated
  - Heller-Edwards Topography Inc. (Box 5)
    - Type Area Calculators, undated
  - Higgins McArthur (Box 5)
    - Number for Advertising Typography and Calligraphy, undated
  - E. L. Hildreth & Co., Inc. (Box 5)
    - Accessory Material for the Linotype Booklet, undated
  - The Hoefler Type Foundry, Inc. (Box 5)
    - New Typefaces Booklet, undated
  - IBM Corporation (Box 5)
    - Advertisement of IBM Selectric Composer, undated
    - IBM Type Design, undated
  - I. N. Blue Printing Company (Box 5)
    - Type Specimen Book, undated
  - International Typeface Corporation (Box 5)
    - Display Package 1, undated
    - Typeface Collection June 1977
  - Intertype Corporation (Box 5)
    - How to Select Type Faces booklets, undated
    - Alphabets and Character Showings of 197 Intertype Faces, undated
    - Kenntonian and Cloister Bold: Two Distinctive Type Faces by Intertype, undated
    - Intertype One-line Specimens, undated
  - Judson Type, Inc. (Box 5)
    - Single Line Specimens of Judson Type, undated
    - Book of Judson Types, undated
    - Catalog 71, undated
  - Kansas State Agricultural College (Box 5)
    - Stylebook and Manual of Typography, 1898
  - The Kelsey Company (Box 5)
    - Printers' Supply Book, undated
    - Pocket Price List, undated
  - Klingspor Offenbach a. M. (Box 5)
    - Booklet of emblems, undated
  - Klingspor Typefounders (Box 5)
    - Klingspor Foundry Types, undated
    - Cocktail Borders, undated
  - Kutztown Publishing Co. (Box 5)
    - Type Specimen Book, undated
    - A Type Specimen Book Showing Machines Set Type Faces, undated
  - Lanston Monotype Machine Company (Box 5)
    - New Monotype Faces produced from 1931 to 1936, 1931-1936
    - Monotype: A Journal of Composing Room Efficiency, undated
    - A Typographic Calendar for the Year 1954
    - Specimen Showings Booklet, undated
    - Selected Specimen Sheet, undated
  - The Wilson H. Lee Company (Box 5)
    - Type Faces and Sizes Shown in Series Booklet, undated
  - Letraset USA Inc. (Box 5)
    - Graphic Art Products Catalog, undated
    - Instant Lettering, undated
    - New Letraset Typefaces, 1978
    - 18 New Type Faces, undated
  - Lettering Inc. (Box 5)
    - 43 New Square Gothic Hand Lettered Alphabets Booklet, undated
  - Lexicraft Typographers Co. (Box 5)
    - Photo Typositor Film Alphabets Book, undated
  - Linotype (Box 5)
    - Linotype News, undated
    - The Romance of Print, undated
    - Supplement No. 3: Specimen Book of Linotype Faces, October, 1941
    - Supplement No. 1: Specimen Book Linotype Faces, undated
    - Distinction in Type Design, undated
    - Dashes, Braces, Brackets and Other Aids, undated
  - Lubalin, Burns & Co. Inc. (Box 6)
    - Typeface Directory, undated
    - Typefaces Booklet, undated
  - Ludlow Typography Company (Box 6)
    - Ludlow Typefaces One Line Specimens, undated
    - Alphabets, undated
  - Mackenzie & Harris, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Type Specimens & Price List 1948
    - Font Sizes and Prices Centaur and Arrighi, undated
    - Types and Prices October 1971
    - Types Booklets, undated
  - Marder, Luse & Co. (Box 9)
    - Abridged Specimen Book, undated
  - Douglas C. McMurtrie (Box 6)
    - Newspaper Advertising Typography, undated
    - Effective Typography and Economy Article, undated
    - A Century of Progress in the Graphic Arts Article, undated
  - Mecanorma (Box 6)
    - Typefaces Booklet, undated
  - Mergenthaler (Box 10)
    - Lining Memphis Lining Metro, undated
    - Typography Layout Kit, undated
    - 13 Typefaces, undated
    - Linotype Border Proofs for Use in Making Lay-outs, undated
    - Distinguished Composition on the Linotype, undated
    - Supplement No. 1 Specimen Book Linotype Faces, undated
  - John C. Meyer & Son, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Meyer Types Pamphlet, undated
    - New Specimen Pages, undated
  - Monotype, New York (Box 10)
    - Book of Select Type Faces, undated
    - Monotype Pictorial Booklet, undated
  - Monsen-Chicago Typographers (Box 6)
    - Typographic Handibook, undated
  - Morgan Press (Box 10)
    - Morgan Press Wood Type Book, undated; 2 copies
    - Morgan Press Types, undated; 2
    - Supplement Number One Wood Type, undated
    - The Headliners Books, undated
  - Mortensen Print Shop (Box 6)
    - Types Booklet, undated
  - National Display Alphabet Co. (Box 10)
    - Innes Alphabets for Advertising Display Book, undated
  - New York Public Library (Box 6)
    - Old-Fashioned Type Specimens, undated; 5 copies
  - North Central Publishing Company (Box 6)
    - Variable Input Text And Display Phototypesetter Book, undated
  - Chas. D. O'Brien, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Typefaces Booklet, undated; 3
  - Oriental Press (Box 6)
    - Richard Watts Specimen, 1826-1827
  - P22 Type Foundry (Box 6)
    - Catalog of Type Styles, undated
  - Para-Tone Incorporated (Box 6)
    - Zip-a-line Tapes, undated
    - Graphic Art Aids, undated
  - Frederic Nelson Phillips Inc. (Box 10)
    - Modern Uses of Antique and Exotic Types, undated
    - The Record of Goudy Types, undated
    - Old Fashioned Type Faces, undated
  - Philmac Typographers, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Index 63 Book, undated
    - Borders, Brackets, Dashes & Ornaments, undated
  - Photo-Lettering Inc. (Box 6)
    - '63 Alphabet Supplement, 1963
    - Psychedelitypes, 1968
  - Photomechanical Techniques (Box 6)
    - Photomechanical Techniques Booklet, undated
  - Pinkham Press (Box 6)
    - Book Types of the Pinkham Press, 1916
  - Photo-Composing Room (Box 6)
    - "Monophoto" Faces Booklet, undated
  - Photo-Lettering, Inc. (Box 10)
    - 1967 Alphabet Yearbook
    - A Catalog of Protype Styles, undated; 2 copies
    - Letter Art Booklet, undated
    - Art Deco Booklet, undated
    - Psychedelitypes Booklet, undated; 2
    - A Collection of Art Nouveau Xenotypes 1895-1905, undated; 2 copies
    - A Keepsake from Photo-Lettering, undated
    - Authentic Photographic Xylotypes, undated
    - Three! Booklet, undated; 2
    - Alphabet Supplement '62, 1962
  - Planck's Typographic Service, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Type Specimen Book No. 2, undated
    - Lettering Styles Display Catalog, undated
    - Advanced Showing of Additional New Type Faces, undated
  - Prestype (Box 6)
    - Catalog of Types, undated
  - Plumb (Box 6)
    - Types Book, undated
  - Polygraphic Company of America (Box 6)
    - Specimens of Modern Typewriting Typography, undated
  - Quinn & Boden Company, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Specimens of Our Foundry Type Faces, undated
  - Rumford Press (Box 6)
    - Selection of Type Faces, undated
    - Type Book, undated
  - Schriftguss (Box 6)
    - Typefaces Book, undated
  - John W. Shields, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Type and Rule Catalogue, undated
  - Harry Silverstein Inc. (Box 6)
    - Linotype Specimen Book, undated
  - Societa Cograf (Box 6)
    - Nebitype Pamphlet, undated
  - Solotype (Box 6)
    - Unique Specimen Book, undated
  - Southern New England Typographic Service, Inc. (Box 6)
    - One Line Specimens, undated
    - New Types: 2nd Supplement to Catalog Number 8, undated
  - D. Stempel (Box 6)
    - Quality Types for Quality Printing, undated
    - Pro Arte, undated
  - Stephenson, Blake & Co. Ltd. (Box 10)
    - Price List Printing Types, undated
    - Playbill: A New-Old Type, undated
    - Amsterdam types in Prose and Poetry, undated
  - Stevens-Nelson Paper Corporation (Box 6)
    - Price List and Supplemental Index, undated
  - Stratford Press (Box 6)
    - And Index of Type Faces, undated
    - Type Faces and Location, undated
  - Streamlined Copy-Fitting (Box 6)
    - Direct Visual Control Method Booklet, undated
  - Edwin H. Stuart Inc. (Box 6)
    - Typo Graphic Type Number, undated
  - Strumpf Advertising Associates (Box 6)
    - DSJ Vari-Type Setting, undated
  - Tactype Inc. (Box 6)
    - 1974 Tactype Catalog
    - Tactype - Dry Transfer Type and Symbols, undated
  - Time Inc. (Box 6)
    - How to Read Fortune in Bed, undated
  - Trans-Art Inc. (Box 6)
    - Artype Catalog, undated; 6
  - Tri-Arts Press, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Olde Type Faces at Tri-Arts Press, Inc., undated